Guide to the Walter Gardner Hall Papers, 1923-1990 MS 280
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series X: Oversized Material
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1950-1959
    - The Houston Post: "Daniel Supporters Win Party Control" by Wiliam H. Gardner, September 12, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The New York Times,: Text of Stevenson Comment on Republican Platform and Democrats' Analysis of It, August 26, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fort-Worth Star-Telegram,: Johnson-Rayburn Team Helps Daniel Win Victory by Sam Kinch, September 12, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - (Corpus Christi, TX),: Realities of Times Bring Changes in Ike's Outlook by Drew Pearson, January 21, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Houston Post: "Drummond in Washington: President Eisenhower's Program for Peace Faces Shredding...", February 17, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Galveston News,: Democrats of Texas Take Aim, Have Candidates Ready by Sam Wood, June 1, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - "Amity Prevails at GOP Round Table" by George Dixon (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1960-1969
    - The Texas Observer,: Hall's Case for LBJ by Walter Hall, March 25, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Alvin Sun,: Across the Centuries: Reprint of the Sermon on the Mount (Matthew 5-7), May 12, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Houston Chronicle,: The Dispossessed - 1962 by Daniel Bell, December 2, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Houston Post,: Walter Hall, Banker, Doesn't Act the Part by John Rainey, December 10, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Houston Chronicle,: Chronicle Poll Covers the State by Bo Byers, November 22, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Houston Chronicle,: Yarborough Likely to Keep Senate Seat and GOP Primary Could Be Decisive in Yarborough - Connally Race, November 22, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Houston Chronicle,: The Bill of Rights and Oswald, Ruby (excerpt), December 15, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Mainland Times,: County Oil, Gas Production Worth $35.7 Million Yearly, December 19, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Houston Chronicle,: LBJ to Beat Barry by 282,000 Votes--Yarborough's Lead Over Bush Is Slim by Bo Byers, [1964?] (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston Daily News,: FAA to Close Office at Isle's Scholes Field, February 5, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Houston Chronicle,: Thad Hutcheson replies to `incredible letter' in column Your Letters, February 9, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Tulia Herald (Swisher County, TX),: The Ralph Yarborough Story - Portrait of a Texas Statesman by Elton L. Miller, July 16, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston County Press,: The Gulf Coast Area Greets the Vice President and Texas' own LBJ cheered by 2000 area Residents, August 15, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston Daily News,: The Role of Lyndon B. Johnson at Atlantic City by William S. White, August 23, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Senior Citizens Voice,: Yarborough Endorses Gore Proposal, September 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Houston Chronicle,: Johnson Tells South `Negro' not big issue by Frank Cormier, October 11, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Houston Chronicle,: Johnson in Homestretch Like Frenzied Evangelist by William MacKaye, October 11, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Houston Chronicle,: Des Moines Newspaper Backs LBJ, October 11, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Houston Chronicle,: Sen. Goldwater Endorses School-Prayer Amendment by Jim Hyatt, October 11, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston County Press, (excerpt), October 22, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston Daily News,: Johnson Sweeps to Victory; Democrats Carry County, November 4, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston News,: Seawall maintenance Tax Fails by Jack Stengler, November 3, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston News,: Four-Year Terms Rejected by Voters by Robert E. Ford, November 3, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Weekend News Citizen,: Businessmen's 1966 Forecasts (including one from WGH), December 31, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - La Marque Times,: Cong. Thompson Retires, Brooks asks Re-Election, January 28, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Washington Post,: LBJ to Sign Benefits Bill by Jerry Kluttz, July 1, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Washington Post,: Senate Passes Pay Raise for 1.8 Million Workers, July 12, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Washington Post,: Increases Retroactive to July 1 by Jerry Kluttz, July 12, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Sunday Star, (Washington, D.C.): Artful Waiting Game by Frances Lide, August 14, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston News,: Rangers Needed, Starr Probers Say, June 8, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Washington Post,: U.S. Commitments Affirmed at Chamizal Land Transfer by Peter H. Silberman, October 29, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The New York Times,: Envoy Will Enter Primary in Texas, January 21, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The News Citizen,: Annual report Reveals Galveston County Progress, January 23, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Galveston Daily News,: Yarborough says 1968 is Labor's People's Year by Jack Strengler, March 2, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Daily Sun, (excerpt), March 3, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Daily Sun,: Candidates Go Through the Motions for COPE by John Rainey and Texas has a Yarborough to COPE with this Year by John Rainey, March 3, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston Daily News,: Demo. Runoff will pit Yarborough vs. Smith, May 5, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston Daily News,: Yarborough, Smith to Vie; Referenda Flop; Runoffs Set in Judge Races Here, May 5, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston Morning News,: Demos withhold Certifying Vote in Seven Races by Joel Kirkpatrick, May 8, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston Morning News,: GOP OK's Votes, Picks Chairmen, May 8, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Galveston Daily News,: County Legal Bills Reviewed by Joel Kirkpatrick, July 14, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Daily Sun (Texas City, TX),: HHH Facing Big Rebellion on Vietnam War Policy, August 28, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Daily Sun (Texas City, TX),: Unit Vote Favored by Our Men by Don Weber., August 28, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Daily Sun (Texas City, TX),: V-P Moves Closer to Victory, August 28, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Chicago's American,: The Humphrey Candidacy: Editorial page, August 29, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Houston Post,: HHH ends Visit with Pledge of People's Campaign by Fred Bonavita, September 12, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Daily Sun,: Police Power Confronted by Peace Pilgrims by Austin Scott and F. Richard Ciccone, September 2, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Dallas Times Herald,: GOP Official Rips Nixon Aide, Feuds Forgotten by Ron Calhoun, September 26, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Daily Sun (Texas City, TX),: $12.5 Million Bond Issue goes to Voters by Gladys Allen, October 5, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Meridian Star,: South Will Spark Growth during 70's, says Barnes by John Perkins, December 3, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Meridian Star,: What's Perkin'? column by John Perkins, December 4, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1979
    - The Daily Sun (Texas City, TX),: Texas Political Calendar - 1970 Elections, February 1, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Daily Sun (Texas City, TX), County Democratic Precinct Results for Justice of Peace, Drainage District, Constable Results, May 3, 1970: (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Alvin Sun,: Brazoria County Commissioners Launch Plans to Revalue all Taxable Property for 1971, October 19, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Washington Post,: Texas Records Show Businessmen are Biggest Political Givers by Morton Mintz, December 6, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Galveston Daily News,: Moody Foundation Report, October 28, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Galveston Daily News,: Moody Foundation Report, October 29, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Houston Post,: Big Gain in Republican voters predicted here by Jane Ely, February 13, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Houston Post,: Redistricting called `help-our-friends, hurt-our-enemies' plan by Art Wiese, February 13, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Highlander (Marble Falls, TX),: Conservatives to Retake Senate by Greg Olds, February 17, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Brazosport Facts (Freeport, TX),: Despite Controversy, Commissioners Stand Firm, February 20, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Houston Post,: Sissy Says Race `Winable', May 8, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Alvin Sun,: Griffin Upsets Jordan in Runoff, June 8, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Galveston Daily News,: Citrus Growing is One of Walter Hall's Least Known Accomplishments by Brad Messer, October 24, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Houston Post,: Historical find - Liberal's Papers expected to map growth of State's Key Democrats by Jane Ely, July 5, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Maps, Tables, Charts, Posters, Paid Political Advertisements
    - Galveston Chamber of Commerce: Map of Galveston, TX, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - State Comptrollers Office, Map of State Total Poll Tax Receipts, May 1950: 1949-50 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - County Commissioners Court, Map of Voting Precincts, City of Galveston, August 20, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Loyal Democrats of Texas, Walter Hall, Chairman, Paid Political Ad. in Dallas Morning News: Governor What is Your Answer!!!, April 15, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Galveston News, Table: Vote by Precinct on County Offices - Unofficial Returns, July 30, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Table: Poll Tax Receipts and Exemptions Certificates for 1955-56 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, Paid Political Ad. reprinted from The New York Times: "We Are Facing A Danger Unlike Any Danger That Has Ever Existed...", November 15, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Joe Weingarten, Paid Political Ad. in The Houston Post: "In This New Year of 1958... We Must Start Learning To Live Together...Or Be Prepared To Die Together!", January 1, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Paid Political Ad.: Just Plain Right by Gurley Martin (attack on Walter Hall) (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Texas Professors Committee for Johnson-Yarborough-Connally: Poster: To the People of Texas, from 1014 University Professors in Texas,... (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Carl A. Ryan, Secretary-Treasurer, World Peace Association: Poster: Fair Warning! People of the United States Awaken! Your Right to Life, Liberty, and the Pursuit of Happiness is Being Endangered. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Houston Post, Table: Harris Precinct Vote on Governor, May 7, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Houston Post, Table: Governor Race by Counties, May 7, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Goldwater for President Committee, Ted Smith, Chairman, Paid Political Ad.: "Do You Know... What Hubert Humphrey and the ADA Want to Do?", 1964 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Galveston Daily News, Table: Here are Results in Major Races in Galveston County by Precincts, November 1964 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Galveston News, Table: Where to Vote, November 1, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Committee for County Judge Pete La Valle, Paid Political Ad. in The Galveston News: Who Pulls the Strings?, May 26, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Citizens for Ray Holbrook for Galveston County Judge, Paid Political Ad. in The New Citizen: Vote Sat. for Constructive Leadership in the Office of County Judge, June 2, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Citizens for Ray Holbrook for Galveston County Judge, Paid Political Ad. in The New Citizen: Radio Station KGBC Takes Stand on County Judge's Race, June 2, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Houston Post, Table: How Counties Voted in Governor's Race, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Galveston Daily News,, Table: Total Vote by Precinct, May 5, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Galveston Daily News, Table: Galveston County Vote by Precincts, June 2, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Dissenting Democrats, Robert Vaughn, Chairman, Paid Political Ad. in The Los Angeles Times: An Open Letter to Hubert Humphrey and the Democratic Party, July 10, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Committee of Arts and Letters for Humphrey, Paid Political Ad. in New York Times: A Clear, Brave, Civilizing Force, July 21, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Galveston Daily News, Table: Break-down of Galveston County Vote, Election, November 6, 1968: '68 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The League of Women Voters, Pamphlet from Voters Guide, November 3, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Paid Political Ad. in The Galveston Daily News: John L. Sullivan spends Less Time putting up posters... and More Time solving Precinct Two Problems!, June 3, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Daily Sun, Table: Contested Races of Major County Interest, November 4, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Galveston Daily News, Table: Results by Precincts on Amendments, Contested Political Races and Special Propositions, November 4, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Houston Post, Table: County-by-County Results, November 10, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - United Labor Legislative Committee, H. S. Hank Brown, Chairman: "Voting Record, 1969 Texas Legislature", 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Galveston County, Engineering Dept., Map of Voting Precinct, Mainland, Galveston County by Marshall Gresham, County Engineer, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Travis County Briscoe Committee for Governor, George Slaughter, Paid Political Ad.: "Everyone who knows Dolph Briscoe will vote for him for governor...everyone!", 1972 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Houston Post, Table: Governor Voting County-by-County, May 8, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Galveston Daily News, Table: Demo Polling Places Listed, June 1, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Galveston Daily News, Chart: Vote by Precincts, June 4, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Houston Post, Table: Vote Returns at a Glance, May 8, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Citizens for Fair Taxes, Paid Political Ad. in The Alvin Sun: The Facts about Tax Equalization, March 16, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)